{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What year was GPS first launched?",
      "options": ["1972", "1978", "1980", "1982"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which signal is not part of Beidou?",
      "options": ["B1I", "B1B", "B2I", "B2B"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Galileo signal can be encrypted?",
      "options": ["E1", "E5A", "E5B", "E6"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a traditional way to detect code-phase multipath?",
      "options": [
        "Using a low-pass filter with Pseudorange measurements",
        "Intermittent drops in Carrier-to-Noise Density (C/N0)",
        "Plot a carrier phase I/Q phasor digaram",
        "Subtract code-minus-carrier measurements"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of antenna is used to mitigate multipath?",
      "options": ["Choke-ring", "CRPA", "Fixed Reference", "Widebannd"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the DLL of any GNSS receiver?",
      "options": [
        "Dual Long Lines",
        "Delay Lock Loop",
        "Data Link Layer",
        "Dynamic Link Library"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What Einstein effect is used in GNSS?",
      "options": [
        "General Theory of Relativity",
        "Special Theory of Relativity",
        "Wave Particle Duality",
        "Bose-Einstein Condensate"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tradeoff of using a narrow correlator?",
      "options": [
        "Loss of phasor information due to aliasing",
        "Need to procure a higher-performance GNSS antenna",
        "Requiring more bandwidth in the correlator function",
        "Higher power consumption in the FPGA"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the GPS L1 C/A codephase chipping rate?",
      "options": ["1 Mcps", "1.023 Mcps", "10 Mcps", "10.23 Mcps"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the minimum number of satellites to compute a GNSS position?",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What does RTK stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Run Time Kernel",
        "Radio Tool Kit",
        "Real Time Kinematic",
        "Record Test Kit"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Today, typically, the largest source of GNSS errors stem from?",
      "options": [
        "Troposphere",
        "Multipath",
        "Satellite Orbital Errors",
        "Ionosphere"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Epoch 0 of GPS time started on?",
      "options": [
        "January 6, 1980",
        "January 2, 1978",
        "January 3, 1972",
        "January 4, 1978"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "A typical noise floor density of a GNSS receiver is?",
      "options": ["-122 dBm/Hz", "-142 dBm/Hz", "-155 dBm/Hz", "-168 dBm/Hz"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a modulation scheme used in GNSS?",
      "options": ["BOC", "AltBOC", "BPSK", "DSB"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
